http://www.salonequipment.com/privacy-policy/

Loading... Please wait...
My Account
Sign in or Create an account
CONNECT WITH US!
Currency Displayed in
Wish Lists
View Cart (0)
Toggle Top Menu
Celebrating 40 years of business!
877.461.2972
Search
Search
Menu
Our e-commerce website is always open for business. Please call us anytime for assistance.
Home
Pages
Home
Salon Brands
Belvedere Salon EquipmentCollins Mosaic FurnitureAdjust A SinkAmber Waxing ProductsCollins QSE Salon FurnitureEarthlite MassageGarfield Paragon SalonGulfstream Pedicure ChairsIC Urethane Salon MatsJeffco Salon EquipmentKaemark Salon StationsKayline Manicure StationsLiving Earth Crafts FacialPibbs Salon EquipmentParlux Blow DryersSalonEquipment.com FurnitureSalon Ambience ItalySavvy Salon ChairsSilhouet-Tone FacialTurbo Power Dryers & IronsWhitehall HydrotherapyWilliam Marvy Barber Poles
Design Center
ConsultingCustom
Portfolio
Schools
Financing
Discounts
Rentals
About Us
Our HistoryOur MessageTerms & Conditions
Contact Us
Blog
FREE SHIPPING on select items! *to business addresses within the continental U.S.
HomePrivacy Policy
Categories
Dryer Chairs & Hair Dryers
Salon Chairs
Styling Chairs
All Purpose Chairs
Kids Chairs & Child Seats
Pedicure Chairs & Spas
Popular Brands
Collins Mosaic Pibbs Collins QSE Kaemark Belvedere Garfield Paragon SalonEquipment.Com Whitehall Savvy Jeffco by Collins
View All Brands
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy Last updated: March 01, 2017.
SalonEquipment.Com, LLC ("us", "we", or "our") operates www.salonequipment.com. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the website. By using the website, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.
Information Collection And Use
While using our website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, company name, addresses, phone numbers, emails, etc.
Log Data
Like many website operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website ("Log Data"). This Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our website that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics. In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this.
Communications
Though rare, (we don't like spam tactics either), we may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your computer's hard drive. Like many sites, we use "cookies" to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our site.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember we live in a day and age where no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 01, 2017, and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at 877-461-2972.
New Products
Pibbs PS93-1 Footsie Pedicure Spa with Shiatsu Massage Chair
$2,158.00
Add To Cart
Add to Compare
Add to Wishlist
Savvy 283 Malia Shampoo Shuttle with Legrest with Tilting Porcelain Bowl
$1,004.62
Add To Cart
Add to Compare
Add to Wishlist
Savvy 282 Malia Shampoo Shuttle with Tilting Porcelain Bowl
$830.77
Add To Cart
Add to Compare
Salon Brands
Belvedere Salon EquipmentCollins Mosaic FurnitureAdjust A SinkAmber Waxing ProductsCollins QSE Salon FurnitureEarthlite MassageGarfield Paragon SalonGulfstream Pedicure ChairsIC Urethane Salon MatsJeffco Salon EquipmentKaemark Salon StationsKayline Manicure StationsLiving Earth Crafts FacialPibbs Salon EquipmentParlux Blow DryersSalonEquipment.com FurnitureSalon Ambience ItalySavvy Salon ChairsSilhouet-Tone FacialTurbo Power Dryers & IronsWhitehall HydrotherapyWilliam Marvy Barber Poles
Design Center
ConsultingCustom
Portfolio
Schools
Financing
Discounts
Rentals
About Us
877.461.2972
Copyright 2020 SalonEquipment.com. All Rights Reserved.
Salon
Equipment
Salon Equipment
International
Spa Equipment
International
Facial
Equipment
Manicure
Equipment
Pedicure
Equipment
SalonEquipment.com represents the following fine manufacturing companies: Adjust-A-Sink,
Accessible Systems, Amber Products, Belvedere, BluWorld, Collins, Continuum,
Cosmopro, Daylight, Earthlite, Euro Loft, Garfield, Gulfstream, HEX
Tanning Booths, Hydroco, IC Urethane Mats, Jeffco, Kayline, Kaemark, Kiela, Koken, Lemi USA, Living Earth Crafts, Marble Products, William Marvy, Mr.Sauna, Mr.Steam, MTI Whirlpools,
Oakworks, Olymp, One World Inspired, Paragon, Parlux, Pevonia Equipment, Pibbs, Preferred Stock, QSE, QuickPlan, Ranco, Rhino
Salon Mats, Salon Ambience, SalonEquipment.Com, Savvy, Silhouet-Tone, Takara Belmont,
Terra Derma, Touch America, Turbo Power, Unique Therapeutic Mats, Veeco, Water Wonder, Wella, Whitehall
SalonEquipment.com
delivers to the following states: Alabama,
Alaska, Arkansas, Arizona, California, Colorado, Connecticut, Delaware,
Florida, Georgia, Hawaii, Idaho, Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Kansas,
Kentucky, Louisiana, Maine, Maryland, Massachusetts, Michigan, Minnesota,
Mississippi, Missouri, Montana, Nebraska, Nevada, New Hampshire,
New Jersey, New Mexico, New York, North Carolina, North Dakota,
Ohio, Oklahoma, Oregon, Pennsylvania, Rhode Island, South Carolina,
South Dakota, Tennessee, Texas, Utah, Vermont, Virginia, Washington,
West Virginia, Wisconsin, Wyoming
SalonEquipment.com goes international to the following
countries: American, Samoa, Anguilla, Antigua and Barbuda, Argentina, Armenia, Aruba, Australia, Austria, Azerbaijan, Bahamas, Barbados, Belgium, Belize, Bermuda, Bolivia, Brazil, British Indian Ocean Territory, Bulgaria, Canada, Cayman Islands, Chile, Colombia, Costa Rica, Cyprus, Denmark, Dominica, Dominican Republic, Egypt, El Salvador, Finland, France, French Guiana, French Polynesia, French Southern Territories, Germany, Gibraltar, Greenland, Grenada, Guadeloupe, Guam, Guatemala, Haiti, Honduras, Hong Kong, Hungary, Iceland, India, Indonesia, Ireland, Israel, Italy, Jamaica, Japan, Kuwait, Latvia, Malaysia, Maldives, Mali, Malta, Marshall Islands, Martinique, Mexico, Monaco, Morocco, Netherlands, Netherlands Antilles, New Zealand, Nicaragua, Norway, Panama, Peru, Philippines, Poland, Portugal, Puerto Rico, Romania,
Saint Kitts and Nevis, Saint Lucia, Saint Vincent and the Grenadines, Samoa, San Marino, Saudi Arabia, Seychelles, Singapore, South Africa, South Korea, Spain, Sri Lanka, St. Helena, Swaziland, Sweden, Switzerland, Taiwan, Thailand, Tokelau, Trinidad and Tobago, United Arab Emirates, United Kingdom, United States, United States Minor Outlying Islands, Venezuela, Viet Nam, Virgin Islands, Virgin Islands, Western Sahara
All prices are in USD.
Close
Close
Selected For Comparision
Compare Now
